fastdrive.org 2006-06-17

# Privacy Policy

Documento senza titolo

**Fastdrive.org Statement of Privacy**

Fastdrive.org is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information on our Web site. 

This Privacy Statement applies to the Fastdrive.org Web Site. By using Fastdrive.org , you consent to the data practices described in this statement. If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or the protection of your personal information on the Fastdrive.org Web site, please write us at privacy@Fastdrive.org 

**Third Party Advertising**  
These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**   
Fastdrive.org explicitly asks when it needs information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") pertinent to the specific product or service you are choosing to use or subscribe to on the Fastdrive.org web site. This information can include your e-mail address, name, address, and telephone number, as applicable. Fastdrive.org may also ask for non-personal information or demographic information. 

This web site also offers the ability to enter sweepstakes where personal information is collected in order to notify you if you are the winner of the sweepstakes. 

**Use of your Personal Information**   
Fastdrive.org and our affiliates and service partners use your personal information to operate the Fastdrive.org web site and to provide the Fastdrive.org services you have requested. The information is also used to communicate with you regarding your Fastdrive.org account. We also use your e-mail address to respond to incoming service and support requests from you, to collect user feedback, user satisfaction surveys, sweepstakes notices, and other service informational mailings. We ask for your postal address because some of our services require a mailing address so that we can completely perform the service. 

Fastdrive.org may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Fastdrive.org ; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Fastdrive.org , the site or the users of Fastdrive.org ; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Fastdrive.org , Fastdrive.org , the site or the public. 

Fastdrive.org reserves the right to change this policy from time to time.
